

SHAZID HASAN RIAM

User Interface Designer

ABOUT ME

Creative UI Designer & Developer with two years facilitating and supporting human interactions with complex systems and software. Maintains user-centric designs while adhering to prescribed interface principles and related development goals. Efficient problem solver with skills in teamwork and delivering projects on time.

CONTACT ME

Phone:

+880 1717 435 769 +880 1600 009 785

Address:

House: 21, Road: 05, Block: B, Banasree, Rampura, Dhaka - 1219

Fmail¹

shazidhasanriam@gmail.com shazid.riam@northsouth.edu

PORTFOLIO

Behance:

https://www.behance.net/shazidhasanriam

Github:

https://github.com/ShazidHasanRiam

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/shazidhasanriam/

Portfolio Website:

https://shazidhasanriam.github.io/PersonalPortfolio/

HOBBIES

Cycling Travelling

Photography

EXPERIENCE

MARCH, 2021 - OCTOBER, 2021

User Interface Designer

Ghuddy Limited

- Communicated with product managers and UX designers to translate project requirements and business objectives into polished user interfaces.
- Analyzed existing interfaces to detect user pain points, recommending design changes and iterative updates to the IT manager.

NOVEMBER, 2019 - FEBRUARY, 2020

Graphic Designer

North South University

- Worked with clients to gather and define requirements, establish scopes and managing project milestones.
- Designed website layouts, templates and unique branded looks.
- Completed in-depth product design tests with help of different software, models and design systems.

PUBLICATION

01. Mohammad Ashraful Haque Abir, Golam Kibria Anik, **Shazid Hasan Riam**, Mohammed Ariful Karim, Azizul Hakim Tareq, Rashedur M. Rahman,

Skin Disease Classification Using Machine Learning Techniques - IWANN 2021:

International Work Conference on Artificial Neural Networks

DOI: 10.1007/978-3-030-85030-2_49

EDUCATION

APRIL, 2016 - APRIL, 2021

B.Sc - Computer Science & Engineering

NORTH SOUTH UNIVERSITY

CGPA: 3.03

JANUARY 2011 - MARCH, 2013

SSC - Science

BINDU BASINI GOVT. BOYS'

HIGH SCHOOL

GPA: 5.00

APRIL, 2013 - MARCH, 2015

HSC - Science

MAJOR GENERAL MAHMUDUL HASAN ADARSHA COLLEGE

GPA: 5.00

JANUARY 2010 - DECEMBER, 2010

JSC

BINDU BASINI GOVT. BOYS'

HIGH SCHOOL

GPA: 4.86

TRAININGS

JULY 25, 2017 - NOVEMBER 11, 2017

Graphics & Web UI Design

BASIS INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY &

MANAGEMENT

Duration: 140 Hours

JULY 25, 2017 - NOVEMBER 11, 2017

Graphics & UI Design

SHIKHBE SHOBAI Duration: 4 Months

SKILLS

Design Development

Bovolopilion

Adobe XD

Software

Social Media/Ad Design

CSS

HTML

Adobe Illustrator

Print Design

UI Design

JavaScript

Adobe Photoshop

Logo

Bootstrap